Guide to the Rice University Will Rice College Masters' Records, 1956-2006 UA 078
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Will Rice College Masters' Records
1956-2006
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Will Rice College (Rice University)
UA 078
7.5 Linear Feet (15 boxes)
Rosters, correspondence files, handbooks, diet minutes, committee records, fellows records, roommate questionnaires and more created and maintained by masters of Will Rice College. Will Rice was opened in 1912 and became one of the men's colleges in 1957. It went co-ed in 1977.
Historical Sketch of Will Rice College
Will Rice College is named for William M. Rice, Jr., the nephew and namesake of the founder, a Houston businessman, and trustee of the Institute from 1899 until his death in 1944. Rice was the chairman of the board of trustees from 1941 until 1944. Will Rice College includes South Hall, the first dormitory built at Rice. It was part of Residential Group Number One until this was partitioned when the residential college system was adopted.
Will Rice was opened in 1912 and became one of the men's colleges in 1957. It went co-ed in 1977. Excerpted from Rice University, An Architectural Tour by Stephen Fox
The Original Role of the College Masters
As codified by the Committee on Student Housing in the 1950s, each residential college has a master, often a husband and wife team. The college masters "would be the primary ones responsible for achieving the goals of social concern and intellectual curiosity. It was therefore important to choose the masters with great care; the committee recommended that they be chosen from the ranks of full professors. Although the committee originally thought that masters, faculty fellows, and student officers would handle disciplinary matters, the final report emphasized that masters were not to be thought of as disciplinarians... The master retained overall responsibility for student life in his college, but his main duties were to counsel students, provide an example, and advise student committees.
Excerpted from A History of Rice University: The Institute Years, 1907-1963, by Fredericka Meiners, pg. 180.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes college rosters, correspondence files, handbooks, diet minutes, committee records, fellows records, roommate questionnaires and more created and maintained by masters of Will Rice College. Dates range from 1956-2006.
Access Restrictions
Some materials are restricted due to the sensitive information contained therein. Each restricted folder is labeled. Access to these records requires written permission from the Office of the Dean of Undergraduates. Contact Woodson staff for instructions. Materials will be restricted until 2064.
Related Material
See Rice University Archives for records of Will Rice College and of other Rice University residential colleges. Contact Woodson Research Center staff for assistance.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
guidebooks; constitutions; awards; legal documents; minutes (administrative records); calendars; clippings (information artifacts); photographs
Subjects (Persons)
Shirley, Dennis; Doughtie, Andrea; Sawyer, Dale; Cochran, Shelly; Castaneda, James A.; Wolfe, Joel; Sawyer, Elise; Wolfe, Traci; Haymes, Robert; Haymes, Jamie; Doughtie, Edward; Fulton, James Street; Armeniades, Constantine D.; Burrus, C. S. (C. Sidney)
Subjects (Corporations)
Will Rice College (Rice University); Rice University--residential college system
- Series I: James Street Fulton, Master 1956-1969, 105538
  - Academics, 1967-1969; 105554 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Addresses/statements, 1968-1969; 105553 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Associates, 1967-1969; 105552 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Awards, 1968-1969; 105551 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - College Masters' meetings, 1968-1969; 105550 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1969; 105549 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1969; 105548 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Diet minutes, 1968-1969; 105547 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Discipline, 1968-1969; 105546 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Financial, 1968-1969; 105545 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Freshman week, 1965-1968; 105544 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Memos, 1967-1969; 105543 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Residential college system, ca. 1968; 105542 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Residential details, 1968-1969; 105541 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rosters, 1967-1969; 105540 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rules/regulations, 1965-1969; 105539 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Series II: James A. Castaneda, Master 1969-1970, 105522
  - Academics, 1969-1970; 105537 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Associates, 1969-1970; 105536 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commencement, 1970; 105535 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Committees, 1969-1970; 105534 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Constitution, by-laws, rules, 1968-1970; 105533 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970; 105532 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Diet minutes, 1969-1970; 105531 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Fellows, 1969-1971; 105530 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Financial, 1964-1970; 105529 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Freshman week, 1969; 105528 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memos, 1969-1970; 105527 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - [The Will Rice] Phoenix, 1970; 105526 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Residential details, 1969-1970; 105525 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rosters, 1969-1970; 105524 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Withdrawals/readmissions, 1969-1970; 105523 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series III: C.S. Burrus, Acting Master, 1970-1971, 105510
  - Chorus, 1970-1971; 105521 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1971; 105520 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Constitution, by-laws, rules, 1970-1971; 105519 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1971; 105518 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Diet minutes, 1970-1971; 105517 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Freshman week, 1970; 105516 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Memos, 1970-1971; 105515 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Residential details, 1970-1971; 105514 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Rosters, 1970-1971; 105513 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Withdrawals/readmissions, 1970-1971; 105512 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - College information forms, 1971-1972; 105511 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series IV: James A. Castaneda, Master 1972-1976, 105453
  - Subseries A: 1972-1973, 105497
    - Academics, 105509 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Associates, 105508 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Commencement, 1973; 105507 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 105506 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Diet minutes, 105505 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Fellows, 105504 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Financial, 105503 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Freshman week, 1972; 105502 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Handbook, 1972; 105501 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 105500 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Rosters, 1972-1974; 105499 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105498 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: 1973-1974, 105485
    - Academics, 105496 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Associates, 105495 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Commencement, 1974; 105494 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 105493 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Diet minutes, 105492 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Fellows, 105491 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Financial, 105490 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Memos, 105489 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Rosters, 105488 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - [University] Self-study, 1973; 105487 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105486 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Subseries C: 1974-1975, 105470
    - Academics, 105484 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Associates, 105483 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - College Masters Committee, 1974-1976; 105482 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 1975; 105481 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 105480 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Diet minutes, 105479 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Discipline, 105478 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Fellows, 105477 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Financial, 105476 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Freshman week, 1974; 105475 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Letters of recommendation, 1973-76, 1978; 105474 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Memos, 1973-1975; 105473 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Rosters, 105472 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105471 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: 1975-1976, 105454
    - Academics, 105469 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Associates, 105468 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - College information forms (A-L), 105467 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - College information forms (M-W), 105466 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, 1976; 105465 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 105464 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Diet minutes, 105463 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Fellows, 105462 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Financial, 105461 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Freshman week, 1975; 105460 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Handbook, 105459 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Memos, 105458 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Residential details, 105457 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Rosters, 105456 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105455 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Series V: C.D. Armeniades, Master 1976-1979, 105402
  - Subseries A: 1976-1977, 105435
    - Academics, 105452 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Associates, 105451 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - College information forms (A-J), 105450 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - College information forms (K-W), 105449 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - College Masters meeting, 105448 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 1977; 105447 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 105446 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Diet minutes, 105445 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Fellows, 105444 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Financial, 105443 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Freshman week, 1976; 105442 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Handbook, 105441 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Memos, 105440 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Residential details, 105439 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Roommate questionnaires, 105438 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Rosters, 105437 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105436 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: 1977-1978, 105418
    - Academics, 105434 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Associates, 105433 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - College information forms (A-J), 105432 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - College information forms (K-Z), 105431 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 1978; 105430 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 105429 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Diet minutes, 105428 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fellows, 105427 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 105426 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Freshman week, 1977; 105425 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Memos, 105424 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Residential details, 105423 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Roommate questionnaires (A-J), 105422 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Roommate questionnaires (K-W), 105421 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Rosters, 105420 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105419 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C: 1978-1979, 105403
    - Academics, 105417 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Alumni, 105416 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Associates, 105415 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, 1978; 105414 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Committees, 105413 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 105412 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Diet minutes, 105411 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Financial, 105410 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Freshman week, 1978; 105409 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Handbook, 105408 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Memos, 105407 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Residential details, 105406 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Rosters, 105405 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Withdrawals/readmissions, 105404 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Subseries D: 1976-1982, 174657
    - Administrative, 1976-1982; 174658 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1982; 174659 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Will Rice House, 1976-1979; 174660 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Series VI: Robert and Jamie Haymes, Master 1982-1987, 174669
  - Administrative, 1982-1987; 174671 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Memos, 1984-1987; 174672 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - College Work Orders, 1983-1987; 174675 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1985; 174676 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Diet Minutes, 1984-1987; 174677 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Masters, 1983-1986; 174678 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1983/1984; 174679 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1984/1985; 174683 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1985/1986; 174685 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1986/1987; 174687 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Resident Associates, 1984; 174689 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Will Rice Day, 1987; 174691 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Will Rice House, 1982-1987; 174692 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Series VII: Edward and Andrea Doughtie, Master 1987-1992, 174696
  - Administrative Memos, 1987-1992; 174728 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Associates, 1987-1992; 174740 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Awards, 1990; 174741 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1989-1992; 174742 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1991 High School Photographs, 1987; 174743 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1992 High School Photographs, 1988; 174744 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1993 High School Photographs, 1989; 174745 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1994 High School Photographs, 1990; 174746 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1995 High School Photographs, 1991; 174747 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - College Work Orders, 1987-1988; 174748 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1992; 174749 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Crime Reports, 1991; 174750 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Deceased Students, 1988-1989; 174751 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Diet Minutes, 1987-1988; 174752 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Handbook, ca. 1987-1992; 174753 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Family's Weekend, 1988; 174754 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Food and Housing, 1991-1992; 174755 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hurricanes, 1989; 174756 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Letters of Recommendation, ca. 1987-1992; 174757 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1991; 174758 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Memos from the Masters, 1988-1989; 174759 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Resident Associates, 1987, 1991; 174760 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Safety, 1988-1992; 174761 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Sexual Harassment, Rape, and Sexuality, 1988-1992; 174762 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Will Rice House, 1987; 174763 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Series VIII: Dennis Shirley and Shelly Cochran, Master 1992-1997, 174764
  - Academic Exchanges, 1992-1995; 174765 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Administrative Memos, 1994-1997; 174766 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Alcohol, 1992-1997; 174767 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Associates, 1992-1997; 174768 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Athletics, 1992-1995; 174769 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Awards, 1993-1994; 174770 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Budget, 1993-1996; 174771 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1996 High School Photographs, 1992; 174772 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1997 High School Photographs, 1993; 174773 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1998 High School Photographs, 1994; 174774 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1999 High School Photographs, 1995; 174775 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Class of 2000 High School Photographs, 1996; 174776 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - College Courses, 1993-1997; 174777 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - College Work Orders, 1992-1993; 174778 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1997; 174779 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Counseling Center, 1993-1995; 174780 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Crime Reports, 1992-1997; 174781 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Diet, 1993; 174782 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Diet Minutes, 1992/1993; 174783 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Disciplinary Cases (Restricted), 1995; 174784 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Divisional Advisors, 1992-1996; 174785 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Entertaining, 1992-1997; 174786 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Fellows, 1993-1995; 174787 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Food and Housing, 1993-1996; 174788 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Graduation, 1993; 174789 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Hurricanes, 1995; 174790 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Masters, 1993-1994; 174791 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1992/1993; 174792 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1993/1994; 174793 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1994/1995; 174794 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1995/1996; 174795 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Masters' Meeting Minutes, 1996/1997; 174796 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ombudsman, 1994; 174797 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - O-Week, 1992-1996; 174798 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Resident Associates, 1994-1997; 174799 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Resources and Opportunities, ca. 1992-1997; 174800 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Room Jack, 1993/1994; 174801 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Students, 1992-1995; 174802 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Series IX: Dale and Elise Sawyer, Masters 1997-2002, 174803
  - Associates, 1997-2001; 174804 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Class of 2001 High School Photographs, 1997; 174805 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Class of 2004 High School Photographs, 2000; 174806 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Event Planner, 2000/2001; 174807 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Financial, 1997/1998; 174808 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Masters' Committee, 1998; 174809 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Masters Only, 1997; 174810 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - O-Week, 1998; 174811 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Planning for the Future of College Food Service, 1998; 174812 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Student Code Research, 1998; 174813 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Series X: Joel and Traci Wolfe, Masters 2002-2006, 174814
  - Subseries A: 2002/2003, 174815
    - Associates, 174816 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Beer Bike (Restricted), 174817 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - College Night, 174818 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 174819 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Disciplinary Information, 174820 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Events, 174821 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 174822 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Lists/Rosters, 174823 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Masters and Presidents' Meetings, 174824 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Masters Only, 174825 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Mastership, 174826 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Movie Nights, 174827 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - O-Week, 174828 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Parent (Restricted), 174829 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Personnel, 174830 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Program Enhancement Committee, 174831 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Mailings/Invitations, 174832 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Resident Associates, 174833 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Rules and By-Laws, 174834 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Student (Restricted), 174835 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Student Affairs (Restricted), 174836 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Study Break, 174837 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Subseries B: 2003/2004, 174838
    - Alumni Listserv, 174839 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Associates Night, 174840 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Beer Bike, 174841 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - College Night, 174842 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 174843 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Diet, 174844 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Disciplinary Information (Restricted), 174845 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Financial, 174846 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Lists/Rosters, 174847 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Mailings, 174852 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Masters and Presidents, 174853 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Masters Only, 174854 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - O-Week, 174855 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Parent (Restricted), 174856 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Senior Class Events, 174857 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Student, 174858 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Student Affairs, 174859 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Study Break, 174860 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Will Rice College, 174861 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Women's Football, 174862 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Subseries C: 2004/2005, 174863
    - Alumni, 174864 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Associates, 174865 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Coat of Arms (CD), 174866 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - College Nights, 174867 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 174868 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Diet, 174869 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Financial, 174870 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Homecoming, 174871 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Housing Issues, 174872 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - KIPP Visit to Rice, 174873 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Lists, 174874 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Mailings, 174875 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Masters and Presidents, 174876 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Masters Housing, 174877 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Masters Only (Restricted), 174878 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - O-Week, 174879 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Parent, 174880 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Personnel, 174882 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Resident Associates, 174881 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Senior Class Events, 174883 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Student (Restricted), 174885 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Study Breaks, 174886 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Will Rice By-Laws, 174887 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: 2005/2006, 174888
    - Alumni, 2005; 174889 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Associates, 174890 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Beer Bike, 174891 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - College Courses, 174892 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 174893 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Diet, 174894 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Financial, 174895 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Food and Housing Issues, 174896 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Lists, 174897 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Mailings, 174898 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Masters and Presidents, 174899 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - O-Week, 174900 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Parent, 174901 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Resident Associates, 174902 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Senior Class Events, 174903 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Student (Restricted), 174905 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Student Affairs, 174904 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Study Breaks, 174906 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Women's Football, 174907 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Series XI: Mike Wolf and Paula Krisko, Masters 2006-2011, 181394
  - Hurricane Ike, 2008; 181395 (Box 15, Folder 23)